# Jaya Jaiswal

Software Developer

Phone: +91 8884281285

Email: jayamayur94@gmail.com

# Key skills

Languages:

Java/J2EE
Hibernate
Web services
Spring MVC/Boot
Angular 1+

#### • Tools:

Oracle
PostgreSQL
Eclipse
SVN/GIT
Putty
Sonar
SOAP

- Interpersonal skills
- Communication
- Time management
- Collaboration
- Quick learner
- Budding leader
- Team player

# **Summary**

Having an experience of 3 years in IT field and looking for a position in an environment that offers learning, challenges and opportunity to apply my technical, analytical and management skills to play a role in the growth and success of your organization.

# **Experience**

#### 2019-Present Associate Application Developer | Fujitsu Consulting

- Working at onsite location for ST Microelectronics, a semiconductor manufacturing company helping them manage their quality noncompliance via portals.
- Used technologies such as spring boot, hibernate, Angular and advanced java to enable the portal making it compatible for both IE and chrome.
- Used web services to interact with the backend and material as well as AG grid in Angular to configure tables.
- Working on Agile methodologies with an eye towards improving on quality.

#### 2016-2019 Senior System Engineer | Infosys Ltd

- Wrote maintainable and extensible code in a team environment for the client AT&T which helped the company manage their vendors and suppliers.
- Involved in writing complex procedures in PostgreSQL and Oracle.
- Completed tasks like analyzing requirements, coding, testing and documentation along with understanding of coding standards.
- Involved in defect resolution post deployment of code.
- Actively participated in defect planning, code reviews using Sonar tool and various team meetings.

### **Education**

• 2012-2016 SRM University, Chennai

B. TECH in Computer Science

CGPA: 9.1

2012 Salwan Public School, Delhi

HSC (12th)

Percentage: 92.8

• 2010 Salwan Public School, Delhi

SSC (10th) CGPA: 9.4

# **Awards & Achievement**

- Won the Best Team award in Infosys in the ECSADMC unit. (2017)
- Awarded with 50% scholarship by SRM University based on performance for all semesters.
- Worked as a volunteer for the NGO "Umeed A Drop of Hope" (2014)
- Won silver medal in Intramural SRM Volleyball Competition (2014)
- Won gold medal in 'All India Mathematics Teachers Association National
- Mathematics Olympiad' (2010)
- Won various accolades in music and dance competitions throughout school and college

# Languages

English

Hindi

French (Beginner)

# **Interests**

Singing

Travelling

**Dancing** 

# **Personal Information**

Date of Birth: 10 February, 1994

Marital Status: Single